{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Steel Beam Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40432/":{"taskOID":40432,"originalTaskOID":40432,"setID":723,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4523,"questionDisplayText":"Type of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What project is the beam for?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4147,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New construction or addition","answerDisplayText":"New construction or addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5137,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel/retrofit","answerDisplayText":"Remodel/retrofit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4520,"questionDisplayText":"What Beam Supports","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What will the beam be supporting?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Roof structure only","answerDisplayText":"Roof structure only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5390,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Roof and one floor above","answerDisplayText":"Roof and one floor above","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5391,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Roof and two floors above","answerDisplayText":"Roof and two floors above","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4521,"questionDisplayText":"Where Beam Used","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the beam being used?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":587,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above doorway or window opening","answerDisplayText":"Above doorway or window opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":588,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Above garage door opening","answerDisplayText":"Above garage door opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":874,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"At fireplace opening","answerDisplayText":"At fireplace opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6206,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Supporting hot tub on a deck","answerDisplayText":"Supporting hot tub on a deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6205,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Supporting floor structure","answerDisplayText":"Supporting floor structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3161,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"In place of a load-bearing wall","answerDisplayText":"In place of a load-bearing wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4523,"questionDisplayText":"Type of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What project is the beam for?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4147,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New construction or addition","answerDisplayText":"New construction or addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5137,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel/retrofit","answerDisplayText":"Remodel/retrofit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4147,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New construction or addition","answerDisplayText":"New construction or addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5137,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel/retrofit","answerDisplayText":"Remodel/retrofit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4520,"questionDisplayText":"What Beam Supports","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What will the beam be supporting?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Roof structure only","answerDisplayText":"Roof structure only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5390,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Roof and one floor above","answerDisplayText":"Roof and one floor above","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5391,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Roof and two floors above","answerDisplayText":"Roof and two floors above","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Roof structure only","answerDisplayText":"Roof structure only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5390,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Roof and one floor above","answerDisplayText":"Roof and one floor above","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5391,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Roof and two floors above","answerDisplayText":"Roof and two floors above","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4521,"questionDisplayText":"Where Beam Used","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the beam being used?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":587,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above doorway or window opening","answerDisplayText":"Above doorway or window opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":588,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Above garage door opening","answerDisplayText":"Above garage door opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":874,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"At fireplace opening","answerDisplayText":"At fireplace opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6206,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Supporting hot tub on a deck","answerDisplayText":"Supporting hot tub on a deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6205,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Supporting floor structure","answerDisplayText":"Supporting floor structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3161,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"In place of a load-bearing wall","answerDisplayText":"In place of a load-bearing wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":587,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above doorway or window opening","answerDisplayText":"Above doorway or window opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":588,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Above garage door opening","answerDisplayText":"Above garage door opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":874,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"At fireplace opening","answerDisplayText":"At fireplace opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6206,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Supporting hot tub on a deck","answerDisplayText":"Supporting hot tub on a deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6205,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Supporting floor structure","answerDisplayText":"Supporting floor structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3161,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"In place of a load-bearing wall","answerDisplayText":"In place of a load-bearing wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","__cache./api/resource/task/40432/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40432,"taskName":"Steel Beams (Structural) - Install","taskDescription":"Repair Structural Problems with Steel Beams","xmTaskDescriptor":"Steel Beam Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":234,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Carpenters rough framing Beams Structural","textMessagingName":"Inst Steel Beams","rolloverLongDesc":"These firms specialize in implementing structural solutions designed by themselves or others. Includes inadequate or damaged beams, posts, columns, cross-members \u0026 other support components.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes replacing or adding beams, posts, supports, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Structural Problems with Steel Beams.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Steel I Beam Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Repair Steel Beams","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":9,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Steel Beams Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Steel Beams (Structural) - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Steel Beam Project","urlName":"Steel-Beams-Structural-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Steel I Beam Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Carpenters,rough,framing,Beams,Structural,carpentry,,steal,Steel","emcCategoryOid":-12010,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":723,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}